Guide to the Stanford University, Electronics Laboratories, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Electronics Laboratories, records
1948-1977
SC0214
Stanford University. Stanford Electronics Laboratories.
90 Linear feet
Stanford Electronics Laboratories technical reports, electronics research reviews, and research notebooks, including three volumes on early traveling wave tube research.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Stanford Electronics Laboratory, 1980 and Sponsored Projects Office, 1980.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Description of the Collection
The materials consist of technical reports, electronics research reviews, and research notebooks, including three volumes on early traveling wave tube research.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Stanford Electronics Laboratories.; Electronics--Research.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - M.E. Hoff; 24 J, 1960 Sep 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - John Aasterud; AF-6207, 1960 Oct 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Paul Schiebe; L25220, 1960 Oct 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Shing Mao; -78, 1960 Oct 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Edward Wong; SC-78296, 1960 Oct 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - C. H. Mays; 24 J, 1960 Oct 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Z.A. Fazarinc; AF 53, 1960 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Edwin Lewis; IBM, 1960 Oct 31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tom Pedersen; SC-78296, 1960 Nov 17 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - William Anderson; -78, 1960 Nov 28 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lit Ma; Nonr 225 (24), 1960 Dec 7 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dag Guessing; SC 296, 1960 Oct 31 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Geoffrey Lack; HF-33(616)-7726, 1961 Jan 13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - W.C. Ridgway; AF 33(616)-7726, 1961 Feb 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - William Chambers; Ord 1087, 1961 Feb 13 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lit Ma; Nonr 225 (24), 1961 Mar 2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - George Sackman; AF 33(616)-7944, 1961 Mar 3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Paul Low; AF 33(616)-7726, 1961 Mar 15 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ed Wong; SC 78296, 1961 Mar 27 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - H. Meneses; SC 73178 E, 1961 Apr 3 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Lit Ma; Nonr 225 (24), 1961 Apr 13 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - W.C. Ridgway; AF 33(616)-7726, 1961 Apr 13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bill May; AF 30(602)-2398, 1961 Apr 18 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Fred Smith; SC 296, 1961 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - G. Sackman; n/a, 1962 Mar 14 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dr. G.L. Pearson; DA 04-200 ORD1087, 1961 Jun 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Hector Meneses; AF 33(616)-7944B, 1961 Jun 2 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Keith Thomassen; AF 49 (638)-660, 1961 Jun 8 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Milton Crane; SC-87300, 1961 Jun 15 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Marcian Hoff Project #6764, 1963 Apr 22 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Larry Freed; SC-90831, 1963 Mar 25 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Joel Hosea; AFOSR-286, 1963 Mar 25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - A. Blodgett; NSF-GP-1033, 1964 Sep 16 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A.S. Halsted; AF-, 1963 Feb 27 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dave Howell; AF-82, 1963 Feb 11 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Robert Morris; SC-90839, 1962 Dec 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Peter Lauritzen, 1958 Jul 21 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bob Crawford and J. Strohbehn, 7/14/1958 and 9/29/1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Eric Holaday, 1958 Jul 7 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - John Younger, 1958 Jul 2 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - George Krembs, 1958 Jun 30 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Milton Hare, 1958 Aug 18 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Nick Andrews and Wright Huntley, 5/16/1956 and 5/18/1958 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Robert Moore, 1958 Jul 21 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Peter Robinson, 1958 Jul 21 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jim Monson and H.A. Hogg, 10/8/1958 and 3/24/1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Frank Olson, 1958 Oct 8 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - P.E. Merritt, 1958 Oct 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Robert Carlisle, 1958 Sep 22 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Network Synthesis of One-Terminal Pair Networks, R. Pontell, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Howard B. De Muth, 1953 Feb 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - W.A.H., 1948 Aug 21 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - David F. Tuttle, Jr. Electronics Lab, Book 5; AF28(099)-83, 1950 Jan 17 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - RE Vehn; AF83 1950, 7/1/ - 9/8/1950 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Milton D. Hare, Book I Unclassified; C82, 6/20/1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - AD Moore - Book 8, James Yeh, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Morehouse and Gardner U-512, 1958 Nov 5 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Morehouse and Gardner U-513, 1958 Nov 5 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Plasma Tobe, Beroza U-515, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Pierce U-516, 1958 Nov 12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bicknell U-519, 1958 Nov 17 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Parametric Amplifier, Andrews U-502, 1958 Oct 9 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lathi U-506, 1958 Oct 17 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rushforth U-509, 1958 Oct 27 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Yen U-510, 1958 Oct 29 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Box of Index Cards, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Preston Brooks, 1967 Mar 7 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Project 3871, Steven Doughtery; IA-10180, 1967 Feb 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Project 1820, James Pybus; AF 04(695)902, 1969 Jan 24 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Project5207, B. Schectman; Nonr 22583, 1966 Jun 13 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Project 1314, AJ Bahr; DA 28.043, 1966 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Project 1302, David Mills; AT(04-3)326 PA-1, 1966 Feb 23 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Project 527, Jim Gilkey; Monr 225(59), 1962 Aug 7 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Project 1513, Dr. LP Hunter; ONR-44, 1962 Aug 23 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Project 1514 Irwin Wunderman; Nonr 225(24), 1962 Oct 3 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Project 4825, Hilton Mello; Nonr-225(44), 1969 Jan 31 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Project 4822, A. Chiabrera; NONR 225(44), 1967 Dec 18 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Project 1319 Paul Anderson; NGR-05-020-176, 1967 Oct 23 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Project 1316, Joseph Lee; DA 28-043 AMC (41)E, 1967 Jul 21 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Project 5207, barry Schechtman; Nonr 225(83), 1967 Mar 16 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - R. Genwood, AF 83, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - DD Cherry VIII, AF83, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - D.F. Tuttle, Jr. Book 4, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Project 1851, George Vendelin; AF-7726, 1961 Oct 16 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Project 1614, Mike Swiontek; SC. 755K, 1961 Oct 12 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Project 1614, Mike Swiontek; SC - 755K, 1962 Feb 26 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Jim Picken; AF.53, 1962 Feb 9 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Project 515, Dave Howell; US 375, 1962 Jan 25 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Porject 1853, George Vendelin; A733(616)-7726, 1961 Dec 27 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Project 1717, Dave Dumin; AF-7726, 1964 Aug 12 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Project 1851 Don, Lecocq; AF-7726, 1961 Nov 8 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Project 1804, Leroy Chanq; AF.7726, 1961 Nov 7 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Thomas J. Beaulieu; 2-KCK-705-94, 1965 Oct 6 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Project 4233, Norman Kauachikea; IA-10180, 1965 Oct 5 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Project 2022, Joel Falke; Nonr225(59), 1965 Sep 28 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Project 1966, Niel tanner; Nonr 255(59), 1965 Sep 23 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Project 4813, Heing Riugg; Nonr 225 (44), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Project 1306, David Mills; AF 33(615)-2389, 1965 Sep 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Project 4250, John R. Boston; Nonr 225(81), 1965 Aug 10 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Project 2276, Nicholas Cianos; AF33(615)-1411, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Project 5402, C.Y. Duh; SD-87-4850-47, 1965 Jul 6 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Project 0321, Baryy Stallard; AMC-00482, 1965 Oct 18 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Project 4822, Paul Gary; Nonr 255(44), 1965 Oct 15 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Project 3812, Clinton R. Hilliland; Nonr 225(64), 1965 Oct 13 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Project 2276, Peter Glandics; AF 33(615)-1411, 1965 Oct 7 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Project 4663, Robt james; AF33(657)-11586, 1965 Dec 8 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Project 1907, James G. Potter; Nonr 225(59), 1965 Dec 7 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Martin Buehler; DA31(124) ARD(D)155, 1965 Nov 22 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Project 9969, Laurence Davis; AF 04(695)-745, 1965 Nov 19 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Project 1204, Alfred J. Bahr; AF 33(615)-2389, 1965 Nov 17 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Project 1613, Mike Swiontek; SC-755K, 1961 Jun 16 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Project 507Q, Richard Lee; AF 33(616)-7944, 1961 Jun 23 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Project 24A, Imsong Lee; NONR 225(24), 1961 Jun 27 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - W.C. Ridgway; AF 33(616)-7726, 1961 Jun 29 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Project 1512, Elrod T. Woodbury; AF 33(616)-7726, 1961 Jun 30 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Project 1851, Harold S. Crafts; AF 33(616)7726, 1961 Jul 5 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - George Carpenter; Nonr 225(270, 1961 Jul 11 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Project 177, B.J. McMurty; SC. 87, 1961 Jul 20 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Project 1900, J.S. Koford; AF33(616)7726, 1961 Aug 22 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Project 24A, Bernard Goloswan; Nonr 225(24), 1961 Aug 16 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Project 24J, George Bechtel; Nonr (24), 1961 Aug 15 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Project 10713, I.T. Ho; AF-7944, 1961 Aug 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Project 755K, Ed Wong; SC-78296, 1961 Aug 31 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Project 458 W, Hector Meneses; SC-87W, 1961 Sep 7 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Project L25230, Ed Lewis; IBM, 1961 Sep 11 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Project 104A, Don Dobrott; AF 19(604)-5480, 1961 Sep 14 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Project 1851, William Beadle; AF-7726, 1961 Sep 20 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Project 109, Jim Simpson; AF-7944, 1961 Jul 29 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Project 173, T.C. Lee; AF 49(638)-660, 1961 Oct 18 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Project 174, I.C. Chang; Nonr (24), 1961 Oct 18 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Project 1851, Harold Crafts; AF-7726, 1961 Oct 27 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Jacques Spalter, 1957 Aug 28 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ernesto Yhap, 1957 Aug 21 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Bhagawandas Nathi, 1957 Aug 20 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Paul Griffith, 1957 Aug 19 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Charles V. Bell, 1957 Jun 17 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ron Keller, 1957 Aug 5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - C.M. Lin, 1957 Jul 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Roland Wondeckea, 1957 Jun 19 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - R. Bharat, 1957 Jun 17 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Greg Noew, 1957 Jun 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pierce Brennan, 1957 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Ronald Keller, 1957 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Robert Falconer, 1957 Aug 20 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - John Younger, 1957 Jun 4 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Jim Jones, 1957 May 30 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - James Spilker, Jr., 1957 May 29 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Macrobio Lim, 1957 May 23 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bob Walker, 1957 May 14 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Robert Falconer, 1957 May 13 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Milton Crane, 1957 May 7 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Jacques Spalter, 1957 Apr 26 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - F. Frank, 1956 Nov 5 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hector Menesses, 1958 Feb 19 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Lory Siegman, 1957 Jan 17 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ken Lorenson, 1957 Jan 7 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Hector Menesses, 1956 Dec 7 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Hector Menesses, 1956 Dec 7 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Robert N. Beatie, 1956 Dec 4 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hector Mennesses, 1958 Feb 19 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Takeshi Soto, 1957 Jan 22 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Milton Crane, 1957 May 7 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Ben Rosen, 1956 Oct 9 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - P. Mandics; F33615-67-C-1245, 1969 Apr 8 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Peter Hudson; Nonr-225 (83), 1969 Mar 24 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - C. Hottinger; n/a, 1972 Jun 5 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - J.C. Lee; DA 28-043 AMC 02041 (E), 1969 Jun 16 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - William T. Rhodes; N00014-67-A-0112-0023, 1968 Sep 25 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - A.E. Siegman, 1966 Aug 4 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Casper W. Baruer, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Marty Mazur, 1960 Jan 8 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Eugene Amann, 1960 Jan 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Richard P. Lagerstrom, 1951 Jul 19 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - David Zopf, 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NASA, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - NAVY, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - O, 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - P, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Q (Iblank folder), undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - R, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - RCA, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - S, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - T, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - U, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - V, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - W, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - X-Y-Z, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - SEL Document Library Memorandums, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Unclassified: Letters of Procedure, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - #12 Moderate Channel 3, undated; Film Reel (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Analysis of Multi-Velocity Electron Beams by the Density-Function Method, A.E. Siegman, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Leo Vusloer, 1954 Dec 29 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Project 1315, Thomas Roqnlien; DA-28-043-AMC-0241(E) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Project 1304, Robert Wagers; AT(04-3)326 PA 1, 1967 Oct 16 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Project 1214, Tom Rognlien; DA28-043-AMX-02041(E), 1967 Oct 16 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Project 1302, Robert L. Bruce; AT(04-3)326 PA 1, 1967 Sep 7 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Project 1302, Jean Marc Larsen; AT(04-3)326 PA1, 1967 Aug 7 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Project 1315, Dan St. John; DA-28-043-AMC 02041 (E), 1967 Apr 13 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled Film Reel, undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - #12 Moderate Channel 3, undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 4444, 0448, 4751, 0136, 0121, 2769, 3552, 4307, 3552, 4307, 4751, 0136, undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - "Broad-Band Transistor Distributed Amplifiers" (Box with with empty reel inside), 1961 Jan 16 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - SEl Document Library: Project 708, 1963 May 9; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Casual & Statistical Analysis of Dithered Systems Containing 3 Level Quantinizers, 1965 Oct 6; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Test 4507, 4502, 3751, 1810, 1962; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - (GIT), undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 5454, 1961 Oct 24; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - GIT Test 0083, 1963 Apr 26; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Test 0017, 1962 Sept; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Penn State M.S. Thesis Broadband Transistor Distributed Amplifiers, 1960 Jan; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Test 4508, undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Test 1804, undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - 1803, 1961 Sep 9; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Test 3755, 1961 Nov 17; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - SLO Tapes 1, 2, 3, 1964 Jan; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Filter No. 4, 1959 Nov 19; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Site 514 225(33), undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - 59, undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - SLO 34, 1961 Oct 23; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - SLO 68, undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - 806-3 Test Film Out From Familiarization Film, 12/10/1959; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Color Tube (Unclassified), undated; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Color Tube Film Test Eastman SO 260, 1959 Aug 17; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Test 3205, 1961 Aug 30; 1 microfilm reel(s) (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Photos, Miles, undated; 4 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Proj. 1709, Cummings, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Proj. 2021, T. Pedersen, undated; 2 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Proj. 1965, H. hewitt, undated; 4 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Proj 1722, R. Sweet, undated; 4 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Proj. 1722 Dick Sweet, undated; 2 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Proj. 1965, Microwave Filter Using Resonant Loops, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Proj. 1965, Tapped Delay Line Microwave Compression Filter H. Hewitt, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Proj. 1965, Folded tape Meader Line H. Hewiit, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Ultra Light Weight Recvr. Dick Lee Equip # S-613, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Proj. 2021, Hi-freq RCVR Tom Pedersen Equip. #S-907, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Tom Miles - Multi-Path Passive Radar Locator Mobile Instrumentaion, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Tom Miles - Multipath Passive Locator Recieving Array, undated; 1 lantern slide(s) (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Edson #3, 1954 Feb 15 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Kenneth Sorenson, 1951 Jul 26 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - E.M. Soldfarb, 1955 Mar 9 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Glen Wade, 1960 Mar 22 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - C. Berton Crumly; Project 457, 1958 Mar 19 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Eric A. Ash, 10/1953 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Panos Ligomenides; No. U-370, 1957 Feb 12 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Kenneth Kotzebue; No. U-367, 1957 Jan 13 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lewis Terman; No. U-365, 1957 Jan 29 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Di Chen; No. U-364, 1957 Jan 22 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Hector Meneses; No. U-376, 1957 Mar 26 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - C.Y. Chang; No. U-371, 1957 Feb 12 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Hector Meneses; No. U-470, 1958 Jun 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Hector Meneses; No. U-459, 1958 Mar 25 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Naval Ships System Command: Monthly Letter Report on Contract N00024-68-C-1076, 1968 Dec. - 1969 Feb (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Handbook Perating and Service Instructions Rada Set AN/CPN-4, 1951 Mar 26 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Report Orders Pending A36(039) SC-78296 Classifed and Unclassified (empty folder), undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Handbook Manintenance Instructions A Radar Set AN/CPN-4, 1951 May 9 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Bender Report, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - APN-FPN-16, 1965 Dec (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Octal Dump of Stanford's Tape, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Dr. John Linvill; AF 33(616)-7726, 1961 Jun 23 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - S. E. Harris; SC-87, 1961 Jul 20 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Thomas L. Grettenburg; AF 33(616)-6207, 1959 Oct 12 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Linder Martin; NSF 6 9511, 1959 Nov 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ernest E. Nichols; Nonr 225(64), 1961 Oct 19 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - John McConnell; AF 7726, 1961 Oct 27 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ian Webb; SC 87300S, 1961 Dec 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Paul Scheibe; Nonr(245), 1962 Feb 12 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - John Walkup; precontract, 1967 Jul 5 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - ERL Tube Lab - E. Steed, 1964 Sep 18 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - R. P. James; AF 33(616)-7726, 1963 Sep 12 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Lewis Meier; Nonr 225(24), 1963 Nov 11 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Michael Savageau; AF 33(657)-11586, 1963 Nov 15 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - William H. Cutler; NSF-P-936, 1963 Dec 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Robert Harp; NSF GR617, 1966 Mar 29 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - T.J. Fessenden; Project 1315, 1966 Oct 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - T.J. Fessenden #2; Project 1315, 1966 Oct 6 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Velimir Ristic; DA28(043) AMC02041(E), 1966 Nov 14 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Michael P. Hughes; Nonr 225(83), 1966 Nov 17 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Peter A. Mandics; AF 33(615)1411, 1966 Nov 21 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Nicholas Cianos; Nonr 225(83), 1967 Jan 23 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - John Walkup; AF 33(615)3589, 1967 Mar 3 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Preston Brooks; precontract, 1967 May 29 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Jack Gaskill, 1967 Mar 23 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - David Ramsey; project 2302, 1964 Sep 10 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Gunther Brauns; AF 5480, 1962 Nov 12 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Paul Bardell; SC-85339, 1962 Jun 25 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - George Vendelin; AF-7726, 1962 May 16 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Villard's Group; ONR-64, 1962 Nov 1 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - George Vendelin; 7726, 1962 Aug 20 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - M.G. Buehler (2 of 5); ORD-1087, Aug 1962 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Mike Swiontek; SC-87300, 1962 Sep 13 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Robert James; 7726, 1962 Sep 27 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - George Downs; NSF-G-22697, 1962 Oct 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Charles Burrus; Project: 2053F, 1962 Oct 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Leo Parfaite; Project: 1516, 1962 Oct 3 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Henry Morozumi; Project: 1108, 1962 Oct 4 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Tom Pederson; SC-300, 1962 Oct 22 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Philip Yoh; NSF-G 21543, 1962 Aug 8 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - William T. Rhodes; NSF GK-18410, 1970 Jan 22 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Dr. H. Heftner; Nonr 225(24), 1962 May 3 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Satish Puri; AF 33(615)-1504, 1964 Jun 25 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Tushar R. Gheewala; OEG 0-8-071112-2995, 1972 Apr 6 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Charles F. Hottinger; Project: 4958, 1978 Sep 18 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - H. Craig Casey; CMR (SD-87-003), 1962 Apr 25 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Boyd G. Pett; AF 33(616)7726, 1962 Jun 19 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - D. Iverson; Nonr 225(59), 1962 Jun 19 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Richard Woodbury; AF 7726, 1962 Jun 25 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Bevan F. Wu; SC-85339, 1962 Jun 25 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Mike Swiontek; Project: 713, 1962 Jul 17 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Stan Zisk; NSF-G22697, 1962 Jul 5 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Let's Consider: Unlimited Actions, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Let's Consider: The Obligation of Universities, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Department of the Air Force R&D Newsletter, 1969 Aug (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Department of the Air Force R&D Newsletter/Technical Briefs, 1969 July (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - 5th Annual Glossary of Military Electroonics Systems Armed Forces Management, 1967 July (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Advanced Research Projects Agency Washington 25, D.C., 1963-1965 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - QRR Agencies, 1963 Oct 18 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Space Systems DIV, Los Angeles, 1964-1966 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Scientific & Technical Information Facility, ATTN: NASA Rep. (S-AK/EX) Bethesda, MD., P.O. Box 5700, 1963-1966 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Office of Naval research Washington 25, D.C., 1961-1966 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - ONR London, 1967 Oct 20 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - ONR/ San Francisco, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Bureah of Yards and Docks Washnigton, D.C., 1965 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Naval Ordinance Test Station China Lake, California, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Energy Commission San Francisco Operations Office Berkeley, California, 1963-1965 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Army Research Office-Durham, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Army Electronics Command Ft. Monmouth, New Jersey, 1963-1966 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Electronics Systems Division Laurence G. Hanscom Field Bedford, Mass., 1963-1968 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Rome Air Development Center Griffis AFB, New York, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - San Francisco Procurement Distant Oakland 12, California, 1963-1966 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - National Science Foundation Washington, D.C., 1964 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Aeronautical Systems Division Wright-Patterson AFB, Ohio, 1961-1966 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Army Electronics Material Agency Fort Monmouth, New Jersey, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Reports Distribution Labs, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Copies of "Request for Document" Form, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Report Distribution List, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Australia, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Argentina, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Belgium, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Brasil, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Canada, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Cuba, undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Czechlovakia, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Denmark, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - England, 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - France, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Germany - East, 1963-1969 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Germany - West, 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Greece, 1964-1968 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Holland, 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Hungary, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - India, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 41)